[](https://foryoupromo.com/)Foryoupromo

Menu

Close Menu

* [Australia](https://foryoupromo.com/australia/)Show sub menu

* [USA](https://foryoupromo.com/us/)Show sub menu

Privacy policy
==============

**Last Updated: 6 March 20**21

This Privacy Policy applies to https://foryoupromo.com/ (the “Site”) and outlines our treatment of personally identifiable information we collect on behalf of our sponsors and for our own use. There are two categories of data processing in which MPP Media Pay Plus Ltd (“MPP”) is involved and collects such information to identify you as a participant and/or respondent to the Foryoupromo “opt-in” promotions.

Agreement to this Policy**:** By using this Site you consent to this Privacy Policy, including your consent to our use and disclosure of information about you in the manner described herein.

This Privacy Policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their ‘Personally Identifiable Information’ (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

**Foryoupromo ‘opt-in’ and ‘opt-out’ data processing**

Most of the times, MPP offers the opportunity to ‘opt-in’ to receiving marketing information from MPP and its partners/sponsors. In such events, an “opt-in” question will appear on the registration entry page clearly explaining to potential entrants that by checking the box the entrant will be agreeing to share their personally identifiable information with MPP and MPP’s named partners.

Such information may come from MPP itself, companies with whom MPP has a business relationship and/or MPP’s named sponsors/partners. If you want to ‘opt-out’ of receiving such notices from MPP after you have ‘opted-in’, or you wish to correct the information you have provided to MPP, you are invited to do this via e-mail to [\[email protected\]](https://foryoupromo.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

**Channel management**  

When you ‘opt-in’ to receive information from MPP, you are agreeing to receive email and information via other channels from MPP, including marketing, surveys, special offers and notices about other promotions. By ‘opting-in’ to the promotion you, as the respondent, consent to receive telephone calls for marketing purposes, even if you have provided your (mobile or landline) telephone number to a federal or state do-not-call register.

**What Personal Information do we collect?**

We collect whatever contact information you fill in on our promotional form. That includes: Title, First Name, Last Name, Zip Code, Address, City, State, Mobile Telephone Number, and Date of Birth.

**Information Sharing** We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. We do not sell, rent, trade, or otherwise share your personal information with third parties without first providing you notice and choice.

With Agents: We may provide your personal information to agents or service providers acting on our behalf for limited purposes. For example, we may share personal information with our agents or service providers to enter you into our promotions or send you an email on our behalf. These third parties are authorized to use your personal information only to perform the service they are providing for us.

Additionally, when aligned, we also share postal data including name and address with third-party advertisers for direct mail marketing. 

By Law: We reserve the right to disclose your personal information as required by law (e.g., to comply with a subpoena, warrant, court order, or similar legal process served on our website) and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, and/or respond to a government request.

Business Transition: In the event we go through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our website of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.

**Retention**

Data is stored and maintained in the course of providing our services. Your personal details are stored when you are a participant in our promotions. Data is also processed in the course of providing our services by other companies in the group, sponsors and partners, when making available the product to a tester, or when a consumer registers interest in one of our services or contacts us for some other reason. The personal information we hold includes information such as contact details, mobile phone number, opt-in data, opt-out data, new products/services/promotions and/or when you have registered interest in our different sorts of services or promotions.

We use this information for the fulfillment and processing of agreements with you, to provide other services (by our subsidiaries and sponsors or partners), internal business processes and, to update customers of (new) products/services/promotions provided by us, other companies in the group or by sponsors and partners. Your (contact) details may also be passed to sponsors and partners in order to provide you with information about offers or other relevant information you consented to by participating by opting in to the service. If you do not wish to receive this information, you can unsubscribe at any time by contacting us at [\[email protected\]](https://foryoupromo.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

**Your mobile or landline telephone number**

If you have provided your (mobile) telephone number we may use it to communicate with you and keep you informed of (new) products, services and options. You can unsubscribe at any moment by clicking on the link in the text message which you receive on your mobile telephone or by indicating this to the agent who calls you.

**Your e-mail address**

When you provide your e-mail address, we may send you information for marketing purposes or other information, including additional promotions. If you do not wish to receive this information, you can unsubscribe at any time by clicking on the link in the e-mail you received. You may also have given your consent to disclose your e-mail address to be sent offers and campaigns from Foryoupromo and they will be delivered by either Foryoupromo or our mailing partner(s).

**Viewing for correction**

You may view the data we maintain on you at any time. If such information is incorrect you can help us to correct these. To view or correct your data, you can send your request to the above mentioned address. Please contact us also at the above address if you have questions or any queries about how we handle personal information.

**Preferences kind of products and services**

Our aim is to take into account your preferences as much as possible. If you are not interested in information about (new) relevant products/services/promotions, then you may unsubscribe at any time. Note: our service is aimed at sharing information with you on preferences for different kinds of products, services and options. A total blocking of your data may lead to your not receiving information on offers and campaigns in which you probably may be interested in.

**Database records**

For the provision of our service we keep database records in order to have a robust control in place on our services (and our service providers). The purpose of this is to optimize the reliability of the service. The information derived from these data is used to prevent misuse of data and if necessary to comply with more detailed information queries from third parties on the basis of (self)regulation.

**Browsing session and IP-address**

We also make use of the IP-address of your computer. This IP-address is a number which automatically assigned to your computer when you have a browsing session on the internet, such as when you visit one of our sites or landing pages. They can be used to see which use has been made of the website and for drafting analyses and reports with non-identifiable information.

**Security**

Due to the nature of the service and the trust which one must have in our service we have designed and implemented technical and organizational measures governing an adequate level of security and ensure compliance with these measures.

**Cookies**

We and our marketing partners, affiliates, or analytics or service providers, use technologies such as cookies, beacons, tags, and scripts, to analyse trends, administer the website, tracking users’ movements around the website, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual and aggregated basis.

We use cookies to personalize your experience on the site. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our website, but your ability to use some features or areas of our website may be limited.

Notwithstanding any other provision, we may also engage a third-party partner for the purpose of identifying users and delivering to them interest-based content and advertisements. We may share information about you with our partners such as your name, postal address, email, or other identifier and may do so non-human readable form to ensure the security of your information. Our partners also may collect information directly from your device, such as your IP address, device ID, information about your browser or operating system; may combine our personal and non-personal information about you with information from other sources; and may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. To opt-out of third-party cookies, please go to http://www.aboutads.info/choices.

**Log Files**

As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or page views.

We use this information, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. It also assists in demonstrating who has opted in to receiving our communications and when they opted in.

**Links**

On this site you may see hyperlinks to other websites. We cannot be held responsible for the data processing activities by these organizations. Read the privacy policy, if present, of the site you are visiting.

**Adjustments**

We reserve the right to make adjustments to this privacy policy. Important adjustments are made know on this site in the privacy policy.

**Notices**

If you wish to file a short notice or provide any comments on our privacy policy please contact us via [\[email protected\]](https://foryoupromo.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). We will contact you to discuss any concerns within 48 hours of receiving your e-mail.

**California Do Not Track Disclosures**

**How do we respond to Web browser “do not track” signals or other mechanisms that provide consumers the ability to exercise choice regarding the collection of personally identifiable information about an individual consumer’s online activities over time and across third-party websites or online services?**

We currently do not respond to DNT signals in browsers because we do not track individual users across the web.

**May other parties collect personally identifiable information about an individual consumer’s online activities over time and across different websites when they visit https://foryoupromo.com?**

No.

**Notice to California Residents**

In response to a California law, we will automatically treat individuals with California addresses or telephone numbers (when disclosed to us) as if you requested us to not share your information with nonaffiliated third parties except as permitted by the applicable California law. We will also limit the sharing of information about you with our affiliates to comply with California privacy laws that apply to us.

**Notice to Vermont Residents**

In response to Vermont regulations, we automatically treat accounts with Vermont billing addresses as if you requested that we not share your information with nonaffiliated third parties, and that we limit the information we share with our affiliates. If we disclose information about you to nonaffiliated third parties with whom we have joint marketing agreements, we will only disclose your name, address, other contact information, and information about our transaction and experiences with you.

**Notice to Users Outside of the United States**

This Online Privacy Policy is intended to cover collection of information on our Sites from residents of the United States. If you are visiting our Sites from outside the United States, please be aware that your information may be transferred to, stored and processed in the United States where our servers are located and our central database is operated. The data protection and laws of the United States and other countries might not be as comprehensive as those in your country. By using our services, you understand that your information may be transferred to our facilities and those third-parties with whom we share it as described in this Notice.

 **Protecting Children’s Privacy Online**

The Site is not directed to individuals under the age of thirteen (13), and we request that these individuals do not provide Personal Information through the Site. We do not knowingly collect information from children under 13 without parental consent. Visit the Federal Trade Commission website for more information about the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). If you believe that we have received information from a child or other person who is not of a majority age in their relevant jurisdiction, please contact us at our email or physical mailing address listed in the “Contact Us” section below and we will take all reasonable efforts to remove the information.

**Notification of Privacy Statement Changes.** We may update this policy from time to time as our information practices are modified or changed. If we make changes to the Privacy Notice, we will revise the “Last Updated” date at the top of this Notice. Any changes to this Notice will become effective when we post the revised Notice on the Site. Your use of the Site following these changes means that you accept the revised Notice.

**Contact Information** You can contact us by writing or email us at the address below.

MPP

Arch. Makario III, 161; 5th Floor/ Office 5; 3027 Limassol, Cyprus

[\[email protected\]](https://foryoupromo.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

**Please print and retain a copy of this privacy policy for your records.**

Arch. Makario III, 161; 5th Floor/ Office 5; 3027 Limassol, Cyprus

[\[email protected\]](https://foryoupromo.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

© 2024 [Foryoupromo](https://foryoupromo.com/)
